it's about to be ownership itself that's
your mistake not the existence of ascent
itself but usually people who jump into
conclusion ah no self means there is no
self well who is then talking and
deciding and making all these choices
and then affection started in the
suitors carefully the Buddha never said
there is not something actually people
asking so his master Gautama saying
there is self and you be quiet not so
master go to me saying there is no self
and you'll be quiet because either way
for this person self is already there
ownership is already there and he can't
see the ownership and that's what the
problem is so do you feel like you are
your own
well my in hindsight when you think
about it sure but say say something that
then you wish for comes your way are you
happy in the later than account of it
something that you don't wish for comes
your way are you said about it means
there is ownership in regard to that the
senses that can experience these things
so then you can't say oh I don't regard
myself as my own you might wish to not
regard yourself as your own but
practically in fact the certain facts
are showing you that you do because
you're still alive well to suffer and
feel on account of change of things and
that's really the problem it's all about
denying things denying yourself
it's just gratuitous ownership that we
exercised over our own senses and if you
wonder whether you are exercising
ownership or not just ask yourself would
I suffer if something changes that I
don't like if you wouldn't suffer means
ok I'm along the right path that's why I
didn't like that self honesty needs to
become first when the Buddha said person
is to understand there is good action is
bad action is a good result bad result
there is the given there is this there
is the practice because if if a person
is denying all of that then exactly they
wouldn't necessarily see where the
problem is I'm going to apply their
effort and then it would be like oh
there is no self 'some what is there for
me to do anyway yeah there is no self
you can say that but there is suffering
mm-hmm you're still I was suffering and
that's what you need to do and once you
start doing the environment you get to
understand how that's what the girl
meant by not self it's where the
suffering is not any kind of random
theoretical scientific sense of
experiment that proves that nothing's
real and whatnot because when when he
approached the first disciples after his
enlightenment they asked him all what
we're teaching and he didn't say oh I'm
telling you there is no self he just
said there is suffering and I'm teaching
freedom from it because that's something
that everybody can universally relate to
when he met the man before that in the
same suit when he was going down the
road and this man sees me said oh you
look very bright very composed who's
teaching did you follow to like develop
those faculties and he said I follow his
teaching I'm I only there I'm the
supreme ruler of humans and gods I'm the
best which is P fact nothing conceited
about it but in this man's eyes through
his own conceit all he could seize like
I am the best things are so big and left
didn't want to hear the rest what I'm
gonna have to say so clearly by the time
the Buddha reached these other disciples
he did as if he approaches him with a
sense of I know what the truth is they
gonna be in defensive but he doesn't
know what the truth is a people won't
hear it so then he related that which
they can relate to
internal images you're liable to
suffering even if you don't a semi
suffer you are lying and eventually you
will have to old age sickness death
inevitable and I'm teaching freedom from
it oh okay like oh yeah I want that and
that's how they started listening to the
motive they trying to dismiss him first
because so then let's see an answer the
question there is no self dead itself
mm-hmm but you should try not on it
because you can just say oh there is no
self do myself there is both there is
neither actually you remain liable to
suffering and you don't know the way out
and that's the core of the teaching
suffering and feeling from it and that
brings me to practice of Metta
well you want to ask yourself why do you
want today why are you doing what's the
purpose of imitation
personally I want to like focus myself
that is my main thing and what's the
purpose be the purpose of that to calm
my mind and what would be the purpose of
that why do you want why do you prefer a
calm mind again yes for your suffering
yeah cousin on carmine bothers you
mm-hmm so why go around the way about it
when you can start thinking about what
makes carmine calm but what this time
will disrupt the mind the sense desire
disrupt the mind if you want something
did you don't have there's a you know
somebody said something of setting and
you refuse to let go of it does that
disrupt your mind so you realize you
don't need to do meditation to calm your
mind you need to stop disrupting in
yourself with your own choices and
actions and then meditation comes out of
that usually people hear about Metta
meditation and they use it wrongly in a
sense of you try to replace issues with
matter now if I do matter it will come
in place of this but the place of your
problem is not in things the place the
place of your disturbed mind is nothing
because somebody said something
obsessing to you is because your mind
got upset and I found something that's
been said to it and you can't replace
that you can only train it to not do
that anymore and then you realize I
don't need to suffer amid suffering
that's when Buddha said if the man is
developed you would endure the
unpleasant harsh insult world's attacks
in the same sense you endure when called
sun-like elements completely nothing
personal about it but you take the
ownership of it and it's automatically
personal and then you don't have to do
with it and then you hear about Mehta
and not you specifically everybody does
like that and then you hope if I develop
this meditation some of meditation will
push this whole thing out and I will
never be able to get angry
you get angry by giving in to anger you
get lustful by giving in to us by making
choices based upon it by having non
restraint because that's what's in
common by the way to pursuing sensual
desire acting out anger acting out of
carelessness is like all restraint lack
of self-control so then you could draw a
line and said it oh so your mind get
disturbed when you don't have enough
control over yourself and it's entirely
up to you nobody can control you for you
and people don't have enough control
over themselves because they don't think
enough about it expect circumstances to
control them but I'm a tradition duty
values and they do to some extent but
you want to take it on a new level
whereby you take control of your sensory
strength of your verbal actions of your
physical actions that's all in the
beginning of wisdom my precepts or then
take you for a rate case it's in some
way and we have to only start with the
five pieces no just you have to start
you always stay within them I'm like
even when you start practicing
meditation then you don't do it is it's
within the five pieces just continuation
of the same principles of that sense of
non disturbed mind that comes from
controlling your actions
that's what literally in it's called the
Buddha said he teaches action in freedom
from action an action is already a
choice it's already on a level of of an
action hey boy it's okay it's okay man
no I think the strangest base let you
know the bosses
so I mean like you have to be very busy
clean then following three six and all
that before we can actually develop
wisdom well that's all at the beginning
of wisdom it's it's a mistake to
separate it it's a mistake to think our
wisdom will then come up try to this
doing that is all in the beginning of
wisdom because you're already becoming
transparent in regard to your own
motives where where your intentions and
choices are rooted and then you would
know lead off this is unwholesome like
this is rooted in completely unskillful
desires in me everything the world can
praise it they can say this is a great
thing to do you have so much passion but
from the standpoint of wanting to have a
mind that is calm you realize no this is
incompatible I can't have that and the
reason why people are entertained these
things is because they don't they don't
accept they don't look at it they're not
transparent they ignore it because
everybody wants to have their mind calm
even people say they don't they do
that's why you always pursue pleasure
and stuff because it's satisfaction it's
already formal calmness and that's what
people dependent on it because they
don't know any other type of
satisfaction except like central
satisfaction or satisfaction free will
and retaliation and so on
so my question is so if the Buddha
intended to not be worshipped as a god
or any part of his musical self idolized
as a Buddhist isn't it acceptable to
visit places like the Galata Mali gawa
to worship his sacred tooth or Adams
feet to worship his prayer the the thing
is not people not all people do there
are neither Buddhists no do they
practice for the same reason so if you
visit Mali Java because it will just
remind you of the Buddha and the
possibility of enlightenment that's fine
and the good it did say yeah when they
ask you what should we worship when you
die they were no statues and he said
make no statues of me he was only came
later within Greeks when they came to
India but they go quickly established
because it's easier for people to
worship something that resembles person
or rather than these symbols that order
they require a degree of wisdom and
recognition however the Buddha did say
you can worship the symbol and Bodhi
tree they will remind you of
enlightenment you might think about
enlightenment you might spell something
in you that you might have maybe want to
do it you should worship like the the
sign of an arms ball which means there's
a possibility to give up the world and
be a renunciate an empty seat the
demands of the teaching is also we told
these symbolic things just it might make
somebody think what about the Dhamma and
that's it there was a sole purpose of
worship but nowadays most people worship
out of superstition and there is
absolutely nothing to do with Buddhist
teaching no but that is what Buddhism is
today what every other religion is today
it's firstly superstition and then
within that those who are interested in
more than just superstition get to find
out the teaching so if you visit Malaga
oh so you can pass your test exams
it has absolutely nothing to do with
anything they would have taught if you
visit Malik our because you know you
you wishes to come true again it's
completely in his place if you visit
because I know another way of misplacing
it if you think you can visit shrines
and somehow get closer to enlightenment
simply by physically visiting you know
stupas and whatnot there's absolute
nothing to do with it okay man we can
only come back through the
self-restraint understanding and wisdom
and so in that sense this can be helpful
you get inspired maybe and then you want
to read the Buddhist teaching once
you've visited some statue or something
but it's a very remote sense not like
and I often come to people to think if
as long as you worship you're somehow
getting closer to Nirvana and that's
just wishful thinking that is how it is
presented being of course nice much
easier then again if I tell you no you
need to be perfectly strange you need to
give up things you like and some things
in do things you don't like you don't to
hear that only few people can hear that
and accept it so it's easier for me as
well after just here just expecting
jaundice and you'll be fine vanna's and
what would they say but I'm suppose to
the birthday you know those teachings he
said about like arms and dangerous not
just for monks but in general that's
like making money but that's not
bringing closer to enlightenment it just
bringing you closer to like a more
wholesome mind better rebirths and so on
but enlightenment you need abandon at
all you can't like give you away in terms of
you can't like give you away in terms of
gifts to enlightenment it doesn't work
like that and let's see that's the
projects oh the problem did you don't
necessarily pursue enlightenment but the
problem is when people then
intentionally develop a view that oh I
don't need to pursue it and I can do
this and by doing these random things
I'm somehow also getting closer to it
and because of that you never really
admit to yourself that you're not
getting closer to enlightenment just by
random acts of generosity and even good
karma mean is still common that's the
whole point that's women he teaches
action and freedom for make sure an
action is good action and bad action so
yes you need to replace bad action with
good action
but now you need to bend on that as well
if you really want enlightenment and for
that you can't have like good action
somehow result in self cancelling action
and you become fully enlightened other
hand cuz I literally we will just
prescribe give this give this give this
and you'll be enlightened but it didn't
never it has become bleep in many ways
right somebody cannot like somebody can
yeah you are you that's why he himself
said whatever is to obtain to be
obtained by the man the effort man is I
have done it and that's why it cannot be
taken away because you do it for
yourself it doesn't depend on the
external factors it's not given to you
like you know sudden divine providence
it's just no it doesn't come that way so
in that sense that's what me looking
really if you're clear as to why were
for and keep clarifying if you're not
clear then you get to realize what you
really want and then you get to do it
properly as well without misconceiving
it and you might be fine like
enlightenment seems too far out of my
reach but let me then focus on things
that are not without knowledge that the
Buddha himself whom I respect enough to
follow the teacher said a layman should
do but it's were layman like specially
the West
oh I'm Buddhist for twenty years
practicing in they don't even keep the
precepts doing meditation retreats and
stuff still drink out coupons like no
restraint and I will see the
contradiction you're living is because
of your own ignorance no one else is
fault but if you were to make therefore
but if you were to make therefore
instead of having a wishful thinking of
your John as and what not focus on what
you are first and perfect that and then
you see whether you're happy with it or
you will become a monk or commit your
last one to the retreat but they want to
have it all at the same time oh I can
also practice for enlightenment you know
have my desires there's so many Labor's
and you have to recognize with your
situation is and take responsibility for
it okay yeah cuz I mean if you renounce
the world it's cuz you chose to do so if
you don't another world it's because you
chose to do so
there's nothing like external authority
or criteria the demands from you to stay
like person or not it's beauty by choice
yeah but it show every choice means
you're responsible for it and that's the
bit that people try to avoid because
it's unpleasant see if I accept
responsibility that I'm not renouncing
the world means I have to accept
responsibility for anything that comes
at me from that world that I haven't
renounced I have to accept
responsibility for anything that results
out of my unenlightened mind I can't
complain about it
because I choose to remain in the
environment where these things can
happen and that's that's not easy to
bear next and for everyone so people who
then try to kind of mask that and then
at the same time develop a sense that
but no I am still practicing
renunciation and everything while not
really so we just need to learn how to
be really really even brutally honest
with yourself nobody else what are you
doing and why you're doing it saying I
want to meditate why why why why why cuz
I don't want to suffer so how do I
suffer do I suffer when I don't meditate
not necessarily do I suffer when I act
out unwholesome a oh that's the root of
my suffering so let me deal with that
and then maybe meditation will come
become more obvious later but for people
as I said meditation becomes extension
of what I want fulfilled for me and
that's why one works not in the manual
okay so I have a question I was thinking
about um so I was wondering what how do
you decide what is like a comfort or
something that you need to give up
because I guess my question so also
another part I was thinking about was
the use of technology and like you know
like phones for example is not allowed
is that not if you were pursuing the
path of enlightenment those are tools
okay it's not tools are not like
necessarily wrong it's it's the purpose
of the use so if you use your phone to
cheat and steal engage in sensuality
spread hate it's wrong but it's not the
usage of the phone that's wrong it's
your intention in your action that's
been a phone if you use the phone to
google the sutras and read the
translations online which of course not
wrong if you use the phone to
communicate when communication is needed
it's not wrong if you use the phone to
just chitchat random gossip it's wrong
but again not because of the phone but
because of the intention behind
direction and what you're doing so
that's why it's not like it's not
prescribed it like like you know you
have those Christian orders but you shun
or you must shun anything new and stuff
not at all it's the tool you must have
shown your responsibility for your
actions but people try to like like like
throw away the tools because then they
would blame responsibility on the tools
see it's the phone's fault is the
internet fault that I can't be
restrained no it's your own fault
you're not restrain okay so technology
is okay and the lab just exactly said
why are you using before
that's it always defines whether it's
right or wrong yeah so if we can't be a
blanket one or technologies is actually
fine or it's absolutely wrong because
people will use it for different
purposes same knives folks you can use
to harm somebody with it oh you keep
very practical can survive in the
wilderness without
so there another question we had was
okay so the concept of you know
reincarnation is a good karva
environment so you know I guess like if
I understand expect when you accumulate
good-hearted bad karma it is because I
guess in terms of what if when you're
being reborn in terms of you know how
you'll be reborn into your next life
essentially how do you like so my
question is I guess essentially like how
about this current life like how do you
either leave it in the present right
well yeah that's that's the point if you
were to uproot the desire from your mind
and conceit you would be uprooting any
basis for suffering okay so that's what
I did but that's something you can't do
in a sense of just perform this with me
like you can't just be generous Hey pay
your way to learn I thing which is
generosity because they're just another
level of doing so that's what the world
say first you need to be sensory
strength to keep the precepts and
restrain your desires and only recognize
things that okay I you know I need to
give in to this or something that but
not like self it's a blanket mode of
being whereby you always say yes and
then only sometimes say no when you
can't get what you want it's other way
around it's more like no I'll keep
myself in check
only when I can't then but even then
means I'm responsible for it that's the
first step there has to be able to fully
accept that you are responsible see
people think they suffer because things
are unpleasant you don't you suffer
because you resist the displeasure did
you feel pain is not suffering right
resisting pain by default is suffering
that's that's why the craving is the
root of suffering not feeling he's done
into suffering okay so if you want to be
free from suffering this life here to
stop craving stop resisting stop
indulging what you feel right here right now and
what you feel right here right now and
the first step is to stop acting blind
on account of what you feel right here
right now
then you get to round up and see how
okay so you're not acting by the body
you're not acting by the speech and then
you get to see how your mind is affected
by what you feel right now and that's
where the craving is in your mind but
you can't approve the craving in your
mind while your physical actions are
still very much engaging and rooted in
that same craving so suffering itself is
like how you how you perceive something
or how you how you can receive it and
how you concede something and yeah that
is because it brings you that something
right yes it's it's it's slightly more
immediate than they're doing
it's literally when you attached by
disagreeable your mind automatically
leans away from it right that's the
default when you touched by agreeable
your mind automatically leans toward
that and is that leaning is the root of
suffering not being touched in the first
place that's why in the cases of fully
enlightened monks you know something
they got attacked on the road and
stabbed and stuff and they didn't suffer
on account of it it doesn't mean they
didn't feel the physical discomfort in
the conduit but you realize there was
never really the problem the problem was
you know being able to not lean towards
or against when you attach by a feeling
and you couldn't do it because you
haven't understood it and that's what
the sense restraint needs to come first
because by default people would first
and foremost blame the external world
for whatever they felt see I I feel this
suffering was such and such person upset
me no such and such person had something
to say disagreeable to you but you
leaning away trying to get rid of trying
to override the disagree ability in you
that's your suffering not what they said
but if you never look in the direction
you remain blinding blinding them and
then feeling justified in hating them
and so on so first that needs to be
restrained and then you get
stand where the problem really is [Music]
yeah how can I make sure to use faithful
path and suchlike in my daily life like
maybe making sure like with my precepts
also that they also making sure that I
know all the right action well within
the work within the five precepts that's
all in the type of right action so you
can see like you can follow five pieces
by the body and follow them by this each
and then you can extend the same
practice on to the mind okay and that's
exactly that's kind of the order you can
develop as well you can't like extend
them on the mind while your body is not
just ring but usually people associate
out pieces are just the bodily
Commandments or something like that yeah
their principles that you need to start
applying first onto the body but then
yes so you're not obviously killing
anybody physically but you might have
harmful thoughts if you're harboring
entertaining thinking intentionally you
will not act you will not harm
physically anybody but you might be
gossiping and slandering somebody out of
the same year we'll it would result in
someone else's committing killing so
then you realize oh yeah yeah I'm
obviously keeping the five based on the
level of the body but why don't I
restrain my mind from thinking bad in
harmful thoughts towards others so you
use the same principle or five precepts
and restrained by applied now on an even
more accurate level which is the level
of your mind so even if you're not you
know you know drinking stealing cheating
lying and so on but but am I thinking
about these things am i thinking
thoughts that are rooted in the same
basis that result sometimes the cheating
or stealing getting what I want on
account of you know sort of screwing up
others and so on am I Who am I think he
thoughts that are just unrestrained
sensual and we're thinking thoughts that
are maybe not
not sensual but careless I'm fooling to
me to others and they're not doing on
that mental
because it is a choice as well it's just
most people not aware of that choice
because they're not even aware of the
bodily choices they make but once you
start restraining that these will become
more obvious
yeah and then the mind will become
apparent right within those physical
restrained and she does create it's like
like trying to tame wild dogs while it's
the wild you know if you keep trying to
chase them or something good luck
so you first put up a fence you round up
a perimeter and then within that you get
to see you get to learn about it and
then become more familiar with it and
then they start to listen to you but
most people want to arrive at that stage
of like full control commanding the
senses in the mind without even having
set up the basic fence around the
behavior and then they hope I mean even
when the Buddha died there's all these
other hands than 500 fully enlightened
monks came together and so let's sit
beside the teaching so that gets
remembered and then they said well what
do we decide first do we decide our
rules but omocha sense restraint presets
or do we recite Dhamma first and you
would think of course you decide Dhamma
says no there is no Dharma without the
basis of rules so we must recite the
rules first
so take the cold one who knew all the
rules and he recited all the rules and
how they came to be and only when there
was completely exhausted okay now let us
recite the the words of the Buddha
himself not before the rules have been
decided so if the arahants needed to
follow that order if the fully
enlightened people needs to follow that
order what is to say for somebody who
just starting to practice it's not
most of the time it is the other way
around oh yeah because in the West people don't
oh yeah because in the West people don't
even have the traditional kind of impose
values and anything vaguely religious
it's dismissed as a religious oppression
you can't even talk about restraint
without them associating that with like
you know crazy Christian times you know
17th and 18th century in Europe but is
just like kill people who don't keep
commandments which is against the
commandment but the irony was lost on
them I guess so and then they hear like
you know the esoteric Buddhism whatever
else and then they hear meditation and
they think oh if I just get the right
meditation that's it I don't need to
deal with anything else and you know
sometimes you have all these other
schools of Buddhism like later on they
came they very much cater to that oh you
don't need this no no you can be married
and be a monk you can do this to be a
mother you can do the end be enlightened
is like sounds like one of those fake
adverts that you can have it all for
$1.99 you know but people believe in it
because they want to believe it but
that's what I mean you you might you
realize it it's not that difficult if
you actually start accepting
responsibility for but you already are
doing it's nothing out of the ordinary
just because you ignore it you keep it
in this projecting our I can't wait like
let me let me accept this first and then
I'll see maybe maybe I can't get more
maybe I want more so you get to learn as
a result of it
fifteen years 2005 I started as a layman
but couple of is before that like
leaving the suitors and no no 22 before
that I was very much not interested in
any of that
yeah but at the same time I was becoming
dissatisfied with just generic you know
sensual lifestyle and I got interested
in meditation as every Western it does
without the religion but I hadn't like
nobody really like to ask for Buddhist
groups nothing and nobody the other
religious groups at the time said you
not in my city so I was just going to go
to library and read the books religion
and philosophy I was reading everything
Hinduism in yoga all sorts of things
Christian mystics everything everything
nothing was and then I came explanted
across the book of thoth yugoslavia monk
in sri lanka in the 60s and he
translated the actual suitors and yeah I
did the first sutras or something
freedom liability then there was I had
that recognition did yeah my life is
really good I was actually working for
an American company more money than I
can spend absolutely no problem with
that but at the same time you recognize
you're liable to things changing and I
could not ignore that most people can
ignore that Oh work out for the best
you see people around you doesn't always
work out for the best but you just
pretend that your life will always be
the best man that you want yet so I was
just becoming aware of the fact there
was nothing particular bothering me but
I was becoming aware of the fact that
some things could body and you won't
have a control over and there was
beginning to bother them back that
recognition so then I sort of wind down
my lifestyle big by bit saved up some
money
cuz I chose to stay out it was easy to understand
yeah that's not the knowledge like
that's the information you have
information about impermanence but you
have no understanding of it because if
you truly to understanding permanence it
results in the removal of any ownership
you might have over your parents in your
own life but you still have the
ownership because you still feel that
you're liable to suffer exactly which
means you haven't understood
impermanence then so you need to
understand impermanence by starting like
not in that logical manner but realize
that like what you're currently feeling
now right here right now whatever good
or bad or neutral doesn't matter what it
is it's already something that's not in
your control and you don't need to go
into like psychological and scientific
explanation as to why it's not in your
control it doesn't matter what the fact
is that it's not in your control yet you
are acting as if it is in your control I
mean did you have any say in your
parents getting old
it's it's even inconceivable as an
abstract thought to have a sane yet here
we are acting as if it shouldn't happen
so you again you can continue acting
like that and that's where you may you
remain liable to when those things
remain liable to being affected by them
oh you can start uprooting those
gratuitous wrong views yeah but that's
implicit you need so watch your nostrils
and you become an arm here if reflect on
the nature of things the nature of your
actions the nature of your choices
think about it because by thinking about
it you stop ignoring the obvious you're
not in control and people ignore the
obvious because lack of control from the
point of view of control is very
unpleasant it's an insight in fear and
awe but it's only so because you
completely ignore it and it only
sometimes it's thrown on you but if you
actually start thinking about it in a
measured manner and stop ignoring it it
will cease to scare you because you
realize well where I'm afraid not this
is the effectual state of affairs
that's when no saying that this morning
to one of the ones that's what like
winter when the Buddha died some monks
were not fully liked in the world now
what would happen now but the monks they
were enlightened they were saying of
course how can that which was born not
die I mean for them it became
inconceivable to grieve over it it's
just it's madness in a way how can you
but they couldn't fathom it how can you
grieve over it over something that's
obvious they have to go yet people
grieve all the things they have to go
and they know they have to go but they
still grieve over things why cuz you
even know the fact that we will go and
only address it when you have no choice
about it same like the contemplation of
you know I'll get old I'll get sick and
that's what I'm gonna said you're
responsible for that because you keep
yourself pretty much intoxicated like a
drunk man with life with health and with
youth you know it will go away but you
don't think about it and but no think
about it you intoxicate yourself with it
while it's present that's why a healthy
man always thing even be healthy and
even when you think about non healthy
you think like in a second person manner
not like something that directly applies
to me because if I start thinking no no
no it's this health is this youth you're
gonna feel that and you know you're so
used to avoiding what you feel or only
chasing what you want to feel by default
he will be turning away from it so
that's what we'll compare the practice
of them is going against the grain
now against the string I was like
denying everything but basically seeing
with things are rooted and then stop
ignoring it by not ignoring it you see
the see the origin of this
oh I'm intoxicated because now I'm
healthy but do I have even say in this
health who knows I might be having
cancer growing in me or something like
you get scared well the only reason you
got scared cuz you never you refuse to
think about it it's like the most
certain thing by the way when you think
about it death as soon as you born it's
absolutely a must
everything else is optional yet the most
certain thing is like the last thing
with people's minds because they choose
to put it last and keep it last and
press it there to be lost because it's
too unpleasant to admit it but if you
train yourself towards that
unpleasantness you won't be unpleasant
anymore tonio pleasant cuz you the dog
chases you only because you start
running away from me if you stand your
ground you won't chase you he won't even attack
you won't chase you he won't even attack
you but if you give into the run he look
after you and this is it you start
giving in to avoid in this and that's
how it goes after
okay yes yeah good questions